



## **Summary**

Resourceful web developer with a flair for writing flexible and concise solutions. Developed functions for retrieving, sorting and displaying results from database APIs, created versatile page navigation features, and livened up stale content. Passionate about user experience and eliminating redundancy in projects.



## **Experience**

2017-09 present

### **Web Developer**

Lansing Community College, Marketing Department

- Developed a JavaScript-based API retrieval system for gathering, sorting, and displaying up-to-date career outlook data for every degree program offered by the college
- Improved user experience through a complete overhaul of the former LCC website, handling over 17,000 assets
- Revised and updated daily content for all college departments while staying consistent with brand standards and the new web's visual theme
- Implemented and maintained a new calendar system, providing a more uniform and intuitive system for students and staff

2015-05 -2016-05

## **Programmer and Digital Artist**

Michigan State University Games for Entertainment and Learning Lab

- Developed object-oriented management systems and game mechanics using C#
- Created 2D and 3D art assets across a multitude of styles and themes
- Designed, developed, and iterated upon user experience and user interfaces with feedback from in-person product testing

2013-08 -2017-04

## **Sexual Assault and Relationship Violence Educator**

Michigan State University Sexual Assault and Relationship Violence Prevention Program

- Lectured thousands of incoming students about consent, sexual assault, and relationship violence
- Provided access to confidential resources and services for victims

## **Education**

2012-08 -2016-12

# Michigan State University, B.S. in Media and Information, Minor in Video Game Design

- Followed my enthusiasm for programming through MSU's rigorous Game Design program, ranked 7th in the country at my time of graduation
- Excelled in user interface design and development
- Combined my art and programming capabilities to become an effective and versatile content creator



#### **Address**

354 Columbus Dr, Ann Arbor, MI 48103

#### **Phone**

(248) 885-3856

#### E-mail

wilhel45@gmail.com

#### LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/max-wilhelmi

#### **Portfolio Site**

maxwilhelmi.github.io



Photoshop



Illustrator



Performance Optimization



**Content Management Systems** 



Gulp.js



After Effects



## Languages

JavaScript

jQuery

PHP

MySQL

C#

HTML 5

CSS, Sass (OOCSS, BEM)